A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Commission on Women's Health, SG 2, Series 4 FA462
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Travel, 7
  Restricted from scholarly access - personnel.
  - Bussell, Mary E., 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 289)
  - Duncan, M. M., 1993-1995 (Box 31, Folder 290)
  - Rothschild, N., 1995-1998 (Box 31, Folder 291)
  - Weiner, A., 1998 (Box 31, Folder 292)
  - Travel Expense Reports - Leiman, Joan M., 1992-1995 (Box 31, Folder 293)
  - Travel Expense Reports, 1995-1997 (Box 31, Folder 294)
  - Travel Expense Reports, 1997-1999 (Box 31, Folder 295)
- Commission on Women's Health Audiovisual material, 9
  Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library material, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique seperation number, as noted. Request to access open speacial formats should reference the unique separation number.
  RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
  Moving Images
  - Special Formats -Separation Sheets, 1996-1999 (Box 30, Folder 288A)
  - CWF - Conversation at the Carter Center: Coping with the Stigma of Mental Health, 1996 April; 27 minutes; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11743)
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please see a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    Scope and Contents
    Atlanta, Georgia
  - CWF - Survey of Adolescent Girl's Health with Judy Woodruff, 1997 October 31; 8 minutes; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11744)
    Existence and Location of Copies
    Three VHS copies. Location: Box: 1 [A0000000089571]
  - CWF - Survey of Adolescent Girls' Health (10-14 Group), Judy Woodruff, Moderator, 1997 October 31; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11745)
  - CWF - Survey of Adolescent Girls' Health (16-17 Group), Judy Woodruff, Moderator, 1997 October 31; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11746)
  - Women's Health, 1996 Oct. 2; 2014:FA462:008; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Women's Health, 1996 Oct. 2; 2014:FA462:009; Audio Cassette Tape
    RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply.
  - Women's Health, 1996 Oct. 2; 2014:FA462:010; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Women's Health, 1996 Oct. 2; 2014:FA462:011; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Women's Health Symposium, 1997 April 14; 2014:FA462:012; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Women's Health Symposium, 1997 April 14; 2014:FA462:013; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Women's Health Symposium, 1997 April 14; 2014:FA462:014; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Women's Health Symposium, 1997 April 14; 2014:FA462:015; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Commission Meeting, 1997 Sept. 25; 2014:FA462:016; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Commission Meeting, 1997 Sept. 25; 2014:FA462:017; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Commission Meeting, 1997 Sept. 25; 2014:FA462:018; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Symposium, 1998 Jan. 28; 2014:FA462:019; Audio Cassette Tape
    Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library material, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique seperation number, as noted. Request to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
  - Symposium, 1998 Jan. 28; 2014:FA462:020; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Symposium, 2014:FA462:021; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Symposium, 2014:FA462:022; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Symposium, 2014:FA462:023; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Symposium, 2014:FA462:024; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Symposium, 2014:FA462:025; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Symposium, 2014:FA462:026; Audio Cassette Tape
    Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library material, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Request to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
  - Commission Meeting, 2014:FA462:027; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Commission Meeting, 2014:FA462:028; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Commission Meeting, 2014:FA462:029; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Commission, 2014:FA462:030; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Commission, 2014:FA462:031; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Women's Health Dealing with Abuse #22, 2014:FA462:032; Audio Cassette Tape
  - undated, 2014:FA462:033; Audio Cassette Tape
  - undated, 2014:FA462:034; Audio Cassette Tape
  - undated, 2014:FA463:035; Audio Cassette Tape
  - #2, 2014:FA462:036; Audio Cassette Tape
  - #3, 2014:FA462:037; Audio Cassette Tape
  - #4, 2014:FA462:038; Audio Cassette Tape
  - Part 1, 2014:FA462:039; Audio Cassette Tape